♪ We ♪ Are the Crystal
♪ Gems
♪ We'll always save the day
Steven: ♪ And if you think we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way
♪ That's why the people
♪ Of this world
♪ Believe in
♪ Garnet
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl
And Steven!
你爸还不让你将调味品按字母排序？
And your dad won't even let you alphabetize the condiments?
真是烦啊
That's rough.
哇，我想看看那是什么
Whoa, I want to see what that is.
你好，SMILEY先生！
Hi, Mr. Smiley!
那是个新游戏吗？
Is that game new?
明显不是
Not even close.
我一直保留着老ZOLTRON
I've had old Zoltron here in storage.
你有25美分吗？我们看看它还能不能工作
You got a quarter? We can see if he still works.
我是ZOLTRON
I am Zoltron,
来自未来的机器预言者
robot fortune teller from the future.
我知道你的未来，因为我就来自那里
I know your future because I am from there.
哇！
Whoa!
来吧！随便问！
Go ahead, ask him anything.
我超想知道
I've just been dying to know.
我会得到我一直想要的好玩的笛子吗？
Will I get that fancy kazoo I've always wanted?
你今天的幸运数字是16和47
Your lucky numbers today are 16, 47,
还有“W”（WTF？）
and "W."
我能拿回我的25美分吗？
Can I have my quarter back?
如果每次
If I had a quarter for every time
有人找我要回他们的钱时我都有--哦，等等，我有！
somebody asked for their quarter back -- oh, wait, I do!
、
Ba-da-bum-ching!
蛤？
What?
这是个梗
It was a joke.
天，我一定是老了
Man, I must be rusty.
离我的喜剧生涯已经有一段时间了
Been a while since my comedy days.
你以前是喜剧演员？
You used to be a comedian?
Yeah.
但那是很久以前了
But that was a long time ago.
能不能说几个你的笑话？
What were some of your jokes?
我并不想讲
I'd rather not talk about it.
你有敲门的笑话吗？
Did you have any knock-knock jokes?
有问题问ZOLTRON
You want to ask questions, ask Zoltron.
嘿，ZOLTRON
Hey, Zoltron.
为什么SMILEY结束了喜剧生涯
Why did Mr. Smiley quit comedy?
你知道的，伙计
You can do it, buddy.
啊！我就给了他有爱的一拍而已！
Aah! I just gave him a little tap!
就拍了一下？！
A little tap?!
你知道这机器有多贵吗？
Do you know how expensive this machine was?!
我--这是个意外！我会赔你的！
I-It was an accident! I'll make it up to you!
求求你，我--我不想
Please, I-I just don't want to be banned
被封号啊！
from any more of your businesses!
唉～
Hmm.
嘿，你会电音吧？
Hey, you do a pretty good robot voice, don't you?
SADIE，快点
Lars: Sadie, come on.
你总是想着工作
It's like all you want to do is work.
我们一起去你家看个电影什么的(͡°͜ʖ͡°)
Let's go watch a movie at your place or something.
没人会发现我们翘班的
Nobody will even notice we're gone.
总有人会发现
Somebody'll notice.
比如有人买甜甜圈之类的
You know, when they need a doughnut or something.
Beep, bop, boop.
我是ZOLTRON
I am Zoltron,
来自未来的机器预言家
robot fortune teller from the future.
给我25美分，我会告诉你你的命运
Fetch me a quarter and I'll find your fortune.
那是什么？
What is that?
别改变话题
Don't change the subject.
不是啊，只是这很有趣
I'm not. This is just interesting.
随便问
Ask me anything.
看看他的脸
Ugh. Look at its face.
算了，ZOLTRON
All right, Zoltron.
既然你无所不知，我们该翘班吗？
Since you know everything, should we skip work?
好吧，把机器人给我
Oh, great. Sick the robot on me.
你该去上班，因为--因为
You should go to work because -- because...
虽然LARS不会承认，
even though Lars won't admit it,
他很喜欢漂亮的完成任务
he really likes to do a good job.
让别人能信任他
Letting people depend on him
使内心充满爱与信任的温暖的感觉
fills his heart with warm feelings like love and trust.
才不是（傲娇了）
No, it doesn't.
而且虽然SADIE喜欢做主
And even though Sadie loves to take charge --
我才没那样！
No, I don't.
她仍会欣赏
...she'll still be really impressed
你的工作
with all of your effort.
它怎么知道我们的名字？
Is it weird that it knows our names?
对啊，我不想说出来
Yeah, I don't want to talk about it.
你想不想去工作？
You want to go to work?
咱们走吧
Yeah, let's.
等等！如果你不够仔细
Halt! If you're not careful,
ZOLTRON看到你将来会进监狱
Zoltron sees prison bars in your future.
ZOLTRON认为你们都对
Zoltron sees that both of you are right.
你们应该有自己的屋子
You do deserve your own rooms.
ZOLTRON预言你不用担心那块污渍
Zoltron predicts you won't need to worry about that stain.
你可以让任何东西变酷
You can make anything look cool.
ZOLTRON知道即使他看起来很固执
Zoltron knows that even if he seems stuck in his ways,
其实，你们的父亲爱你们
deep down, your father really loves you.
怎么样了？
How's it going out here?
好极了！
Great!
我真的感觉
I really feel like
我对人们的生活产生了积极的影响
I'm making a positive change in people's lives.
他们给你钱了吗？
Are they paying you for it?
Yes, sir!
保持住，ZOLTRON!
Then keep it up, Zoltron!
好！
Sure!
呃...占卜机？
Hmm, a fortune-telling machine.
这应该值得一试
This should be good for a laugh.
没错
That's right.
我是ZOLTRON！
I am Zoltron!
哔哔
Beep, boop!
给我你的问题和金钱
Give me your questions and your money.
来这里是个错误吗？
Was it a mistake to come here?
ZOLTRON说，呃...
Zoltron says, uh...
显然不是？
of course not?
呃...
Um...
FUNLAND对所有人都很有趣
Funland is fun for all ages.
和他聊聊有用吗？
Will talking to him make any difference?
任何效果？
Any difference at all?
ZOLTRON并不确定
Zoltron isn't sure.
对ZOLTRON人类情感太过复杂
Human emotions are really complicated for Zoltron.
说人话
Tell me the truth.
我真的将身边所有人赶走吗？
Do I really just drive everyone around me away?
ZOLTRON说你今天的幸运数字是
Z-Zoltron says your lucky numbers for today
16，47和“W”（就不能换个？）
are 16, 47, and "W."
回头再见？
Come back later?
我最后的25美分
My final quarter.
甚至硬币都不想和我在一起
Even coins don't want to be around me.
可怜的人
Poor guy.
我希望我知道该告诉他什么
I wish I knew what to tell him.
假如我能像石榴那样看见未来
If only I could see into the future like Garnet can.
我就知道你会这么说。石榴！
I knew you'd say that. Garnet!
我--我需要你--未来
I-I need your help with -- The future.
对！我需要那个
Oh, yeah! I need some of that.
我能借一下你的预见能力吗？
Can I borrow your future vision?
我想帮帮刚认识的一个陌生人
I want to help some random stranger I just met.
看来是对我的能力的合理运用
That seems like an appropriate use of my powers.
走你
There you go.
应该能作用一会
That should last a little while.
尽量准时回家吃饭！
Try to be home in time for dinner!
谢谢，石榴！
Thanks, Garnet!
他准备好回答你的问题了
He's ready to answer your question.
用这个
Use this.
如果他现在见到我他会说什么？
What would he say if he saw me now?
他会说"很高兴见到你"
He'll say, "I'm happy to see you."
你在说谎
You're lying.
没人见到我会很高兴
Nobody's happy to see me.
他会说“好久不见”
He'll say, "It's been too long."
我来的太晚了？
I'm too late?
我该早点来！
I should've come sooner!
我不知道，我只是个穿戏服的男孩！
I don't know, I'm just a boy in a costume!
显然
Of course.
我生命中的一切都很让人失望
Everything in my life's a disappointment.
ZOLTRON看到...
Zoltron sees...
不管你做什么将来都很忧郁
sadness in your future no matter what you do.
这听起来应该是对的
That sounds about right.
我猜SMILEY和FROWNEY的生涯
I guess the curtain really did close
的确落下帷幕了
on Mr. Smiley and Mr. Frowney.
你来这找SMILEY
You're here to see Mr. Smiley?!
没人怀念我们的演出，即使是他
Nobody misses our act, not even him.
我不知道为什么我要对机器说这些
I don't know why I'm talking to a machine.
我还是坐车走吧
I'll just get on the bus and leave.
ZOLTRON说那是你医生问题
Zoltron says that's a question for your doctor.
SMILEY！SMILEY！
Uh, Mr. Smiley! Mr. Smiley!
嘿，不要破坏角色！
Hey, don't break character.
你今天已经破坏太多东西了
You broke enough things today.
我遇到了FROWNEY。蛤？！
I met Mr. Frowney. What?!
他在镇上
He's in town.
呃，你怎么知道他的？
Uh, how did you know him?
我们以前...有故事
We used to have a... routine.
哦！喜剧
Oh! Comedy.
但他看起来并不高兴
But he didn't seem very funny.
实际上，他非常抑郁
Actually, he was really depressing.
对，他就是那样
Yeah, that was the bit.
至少，我以为是
At least, I thought it was,
但即使在台下，他仍然很伤心
but even offstage, he was always sad.
没有事能让他高兴，即使是坐满的观众席
Nothing would cheer him up, not even a packed house,
热烈持久的掌声，甚至是我本人
not a standing ovation, not even me.
而且，我试过
And, boy, did I try.
好吧，他正要坐车离开镇上
Well, he's about to leave town on a bus.
你应该在一切太晚之前和他谈谈！
You should go talk to him before it's too late!
我不知道会发生什么
I don't know what'd happen if I did.
噢！遇见你很有趣
Wow! Funny running into you.
当然，我还是个“包袱”，不是吗？
Of course. I'm still a punchline, aren't I?
嘿！哇！你看起来好极了！
Hey! Wow! You look great!
那是你最好的笑话了
That's your best joke yet.
嗨，伙计！
Hi, buddy!
你就只有这些吗？
Is that all you have to say?
ZOLTRON看到你的未来充满悲伤
Zoltron sees sadness in your future,
无论你做什么
no matter what you do.
呃
Ugh.
算了，史蒂文
Come on, Steven. Drop the act.
等等
Wait a second.
你说你之前总是想让他高兴
You said you were always trying to make him happy.
他知道他让你伤心吗？
Did he even know that he was making you sad?
你说他要坐公交车？
You said he was getting on a bus?
对
Yeah.
HAROLD？QUENTIN
Harold? Quentin.
你怎么知道我在这？
How'd you know I was here?
来自未来的机器小子告诉的我
Little robot boy from the future told me.
呃，Hi，Again
Uh, hi, again.
他会动！
He came to life!
不，笨蛋！
No, fool.
你是来笑话我的吗？
Did you just come here to laugh at me?
不！
No!
我来告诉你
I'm here to tell you that...
我希望我们的演出成功
I wanted it to work -- our act.
但那并不能让你高兴
But it wasn't making you happy.
我只希望你认真对待
I just wanted you to take it seriously.
我只想让你高兴
And I just wanted you to have fun.
哦
Oh.
我猜那永远不会有用
I guess it was never going to work.
但我真的认为我们能做些什么
But I really thought we had something.
你过得不好吧，FROWNEY？
You having a bad day, Frowney?
糟透了
Horrible.
好吧，你为什么不出去走走？
Well, why don't you go outside?!
太阳总会让我高兴！
The sun always cheers me up!
我试过，但在下雨
I did, but it rained.
你为什么不用把伞？
Why don't you use an umbrella?
我试过，但伞被吹走了
I did, but it blew away.
哦！你一定被“电”到了
Ooh! You must have been shocked!
是啊，那是我被雷劈时
Yeah, that's when the lightning hit me.
噢！
Oh!
SMILEY，你沮丧时做什么？
Smiley, what do you do when you're feeling down?
我就把我的FROWN翻过来啊！（浓浓的CP感）
I just take my frown and turn it around!
嘿，你毁了包袱了！
Hey, you're ruining the bit!
我以为你是个专业人士
I thought you were a professional.
我觉得我总算知道笑点了
I think I finally got the joke.
好吧，我猜我的债还清了
Well, I guess my debt is repaid.
史蒂文，那机器值几千刀
Steven, that machine cost thousands of dollars.
ZOLTRON看到了未来抽筋的腿
Zoltron sees cramped legs in his future.
♪